Okay, it's time for us to move on from
codeex and move to anti-gravity,
the last the fourth of our list of four.
And uh you know, I can't resist but
having this up a little bit more. I
think that obviously Codex did a
fantastic job. The bar is high for
anti-gravity. It's worth pointing out
that the reason codeex did so well is
because we are using the absolute
frontier frontier model now. I whilst we
we had it set to pick its own model
before but I'm I'm pretty sure that with
cursor we were using composer which is
cursor's internal lowerc cost model that
that they have built um optimized for
cursor that's good but not at codeex
level not not at GPT 5.2 2 codeex level
and then after that I believe when we
were using GitHub copilot I was using
Claude Haiku 4.5 which is good but again
it's a smaller model uh codeex 5.2 to
and on high reasoning. Really strong
model. Strong model means strong results
that you can see for sure. Okay, enough
on to anti-gravity. All right. Well, I
am back. I'm back in cursor again. I'm
back in the instant project in cursor
because this is where we go to reset
things. We might as well. It's just like
a a useful terminal to have open. I'm
still in the projects directory. If you
do a pwd, make sure that you are in
projects or do cd dot dot if you're
inside instant. And then what I'm going
to do, of course, as before, is I'm
going to rename by doing move mv the
cambban folder, the whole folder to be
codeex_ban.
And once I've done this, that is that
has been renamed. There's no more
camban. And I can now do a git clone to
bring back down again. There it is.
We've got ourselves a new fresh camban.
It's time for us to try out
anti-gravity. Okay, here we are at
anti-gravity's website. It's at
anti-gravity.google.
Uh, cool URL. Uh, and so it says
experience liftoff with the next
generation IDE. And there is a download
for Mac OS. And I'm guessing you've got
a download for and whatever your
platform is, but there's also a download
button up here where you can actually
pick the one that you want. and you
should then download it. And if you're
on a Mac, you'll have something where,
as usual, you drag the icon into
applications. If you're on a PC, you got
a little wizard. When you launch it,
there'll be a few questions. You should
just pick the defaults. Stick with what
it wants. Pick whatever color scheme you
like. Uh for everything else, just stick
with the defaults. Go through it. And it
should open up. And I'm guessing that
you're going to see something that's
going to look surprisingly familiar.
Let's see. Okay. So, first up, first up,
it looks kind of similar to Cursor again
and to VS Code. And that's because it is
VS Code again like Cursor. It is just a
clone of VS Code, a fork. They've remade
VS Code for anti-gravity. That's why
it's similar. It's because it's the same
thing. And you may see exactly the
screen I've got here. And if not, guess
what you do? You go to file and new
window. Uh, and then you will see this.
Uh, surprising, huh? Uh now you should
have already signed into Google with a
Google or with a Google account as part
of of downloading this but if not over
here on the top right this is where you
you set up your your Google or login and
would log in to Google in the usual way.
Uh and so that's that's how we've got to
where we are. And you can see that we're
facing a screen which has the usual
stuff with an open folder and an agent
conversation. This time it's on the
right. And uh it's time for us to uh to
open a folder. Okay, I'm pressing open
folder. I'm going to go into projects.
I'm going to go into Canban and I'm
going to open it. And here we have a
very familiar looking screen with a
middle area files on the on the left and
over here on the right is our agent
chat. And uh it's telling us about uh
Gemini 3 flash frontier level
intelligence blazing fast speed. Okay.
And a generous and more generous quotas.
Okay. Um, and so just just to take you
through what we see here. First up, you
can see, hang on, let me just dismiss
this. You can see that there is an
dismiss that you can see there's the
ability to choose between a planning
mode or or not. We'll leave it on
planning mode. We've got a selection of
models. Uh, and interestingly, you can
see that Google offers the anthropic
models as well as using the open-source
version of GPTOSS.
Um, but we are going to uh leave it here
and uh yeah, we we can now uh we can now
give this a whirl. All right. And if I
could draw your attention here to the
settings, anti-gravity settings on the
bottom here. Click there. Up comes a few
things that we can we can mess around
with. Uh first of all, agent autofix
lints. So, so a lint error is when the
code doesn't pass some basic checks
about the way that it's been structured.
And you can uh set that on, which we
will do, which means that it will fix
any of those kinds of errors that
surface. Good practice to do that. Uh
and now here is like being able to
control yolo mode. If in doubt, leave
this on request reviews so that it needs
to check with you before, but I'm going
to put this on to always proceed and
always proceed. There's a rather nice
agent decides option here where it can
decide whether or not it wants to ask
you for permission, but I'm going to be
yoloing all the way today. You should
only do that if you're comfortable with
it. All right, so those are some
settings for us. Uh, and now we've got
this on planning mode. We're almost
ready to go. There's one more thing we
need to do. having a single file called
agents.md
has has been something of a sort of
evolving standard that people have just
kind of adopted although as you'll see
Claude code uses claude.mmd but but
otherwise very similar but anti-gravity
has not adopted the standard they've
gone a different direction so we are not
going to use agents.md
but instead we're going to click here
select all and copy all of that so just
edit menu sect all edit menu copy or or
command Command A, command C on a Mac,
control arr C on a PC. All right. And
now instead of that, we're going to put
this somewhere else. Okay. We're going
to create a new folder in the root in
the project root in in Camban. Right
click anywhere here, select new folder,
and we're going to call it agent like
so. And then within agent is like a
special folder that anti-gravity
expects. And you can have different
folders within this that tell it about
different things. And in particular,
there's an important folder called rules
that tells it it's rules. And then
within this folder, you can make
markdown files. And we are only going to
have one. And we will call it uh new
file. We can call it anything we want,
but we'll call it like like a um uh
strategy.
MD. And when we do that, it comes up
with this special look. It's expecting
this to be in a certain way. First of
all, there is an activation mode which
is telling anti-gravity in what
circumstances does it need to read all
of this into context. All right. And so
we are going to say always on. It could
also be manual. It could be model
decision if we wanted the model to be
able to choose. And I'm now going to
paste in the content which is the whole
of our agents.md and save that. And it's
done. Always remember to save by the
way. Uh, command S on a Mac, control S
on a PC. Make sure that the dot
disappears. So, that is a saved file.
Okay, we've saved that. I'm now I'm
actually going to delete this agents.mmd
to avoid any confusion here. We've only
got our single rule, our strategy.mmd in
the rules directory within the aagent
directory in the camb project route. And
with that, we're actually ready to go.
And so over here on the right, I'm going
to say to Gemini that, uh, please go
ahead.
Go ahead
and see what it does. Uh, and it's off.
And we're using, of course, uh, oh,
we're using Gemini 3 Pro. I've left it
on. Uh, okay. Gemini 3 Pro high. So,
this is on a big tier of Gemini. We're
going with the strongest version. And,
uh, we will see how it fares with this.
I will see you back here in a moment.
Okay. Well, it's completed. It's
finished. It's given me this summary
here. The KBAN MVP walkthrough with this
nice little thing with a apparently a
screenshot of it moving. How about that?
Is that for real? Is this what it's
actually going to look like? That would
be cool. It's got like a recording of
it. Isn't that crazy? And then here is
the instructions on how to run it. Um,
okay. And then we'll see here. It wants
me to to accept all the changes that it
made. And, uh, it seems to be ready for
me to try it. I do believe it is
actually already running. So, uh, okay,
let's bring up a browser. Uh, and, uh,
let's see. Let's see how it does. Okay,
so this is what I see in a browser.
First of all, I should point out
something. You may have seen that while
this was running, it was actually
bringing up browsers and testing it
itself, checking the screens look good.
That's how I did that screen recording.
And so, I know it was actually real
screen recording. Uh and it also brought
up this thing called called playrights
which is where it drives a browser with
browser automation software to run a
series of tests. Uh and uh you can also
you can see that it in in some of these
tests it was failing and it fixed them
and then it would then saw success. For
some reason it didn't actually seem to
fix that last one but but anyways it was
working away beavering away doing all of
this and it's time for us to see what it
actually looks like. And here it is.
This is the result. Here is the result
from Gemini uh through anti-gravity.
Let's see what we make of it. And first
up, I'd say I think it looks pretty
good. It looks fresh and clean. Uh and
think I think it looks very good. We can
flip things around. Yes, that all seems
to work. Let's move that over there.
Let's uh see if we can add a card. Enter
cutter. Okay, that's a bit janky having
like a local host thing there, but we'll
say uh okay. Uh and then uh there it is.
And now can we come in? Oh, we can't
actually add a description to that. That
seems a bit mediocre. Uh, and can we
change this title? Yes, we can. Um, this
is good. There we go. Uh, that's done.
Okay, that's great. So, I'd say that
this adding a new card is the only thing
that feels a little bit simplistic.
Let's see if we can't improve that.